双峰  第三季第二集
原创翻译  双语字幕
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
翻译     苏小黛 胖爱 Silence 小仓 吃冰棒 詹木头 小酸奶
翻译     Lynn_宁  TheWalkingNerd  一只虾  Reginamoon
校对     小酸奶
时间轴     啾啾啾  吃土少女  知之
我只能让你俩短暂地见一面
Now...I can only give you a short visit.
谢谢  戴夫
Thank you, Dave.
后期     8T
总监     小酸奶
乔治说他们不会让你保释的
George says they're not gonna let you out on bail.
我...
I'm--
我麻烦大了
I'm in so much trouble.
我...
I have--
我得告诉你件事
I have to tell you something.
我不在那里
I wasn't there,
但是我...
but I h--
我那晚做了个梦
I had a dream that night
是...
that--
我在她公寓里
that I was in her apartment.
你在那里
You were there.
那里有你的指纹
Your fingerprints are there.
不  我对你发誓  我不在那里
No, I sw--I swear to you, I wasn't there.
我发誓  那是个梦
I swear to you, it was a dream!
去你大爷的
Fuck you.
你个混蛋
You fucking bastard!
我知道你的婚外情
I've known about this affair.
我知道很久了
I've known about this affair all along.
现在  你看着我
Now, you lookee here.
我知道你和乔治的事
I know about you and George
也许还有别人也知道
and maybe somebody else too!
你完了
You're going down.
终身监禁  比尔
Life in prison, Bill.
终身监禁
Life in prison.
再见  比尔
Good-bye, Bill.
天啊
Oh, my God.
天...
Oh, my--
天啊
oh, my God.
天...
Oh, my--
天啊
oh, my God.
乔治
George.
菲莉斯
Phyllis.
他怎么样
How is he?
他知道了
He knows.
不要送我出去
Don't walk me out.
等等在我家见
I'll see you later at my place.
他怎么样了
How's he doing?
他
Well, he's, uh,
不得不承认  他是吓坏了
pretty shook up, I have to admit.
菲莉斯呢
And Phyllis?
我想她今天过得很糟
She's had a really rough day, I believe.
是啊
Yes. I understand.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你在这干什么
What are you doing here?
你做得很好
You did good.
你很好地遵从了本性
You follow human nature perfectly.
这是乔治的枪
This is George's gun.
内华达州  拉斯维加斯
罗杰  进来
Roger, come in here.
告诉她她被录用了
Tell her she has the job.
托德先生
Mr. Todd?
什么事  罗杰
Yes, Roger?
我能问你个问题吗
Can I ask you a question?
说吧
Go ahead.
你为什么让他逼你
Why do you let him make you...
做这些事
do these things?
罗杰
Roger...
你最好祈祷
...you better hope
永远别和他这种人扯上关系
that you never get involved with someone like him.
这辈子别遇上
Never have someone like him
他这种人
in your life.
杰克  你的三份晚餐都没怎么吃呢
Jack, you barely touched your three dinners.
听达雅说
Darya said something about you,
你在担心明天的事
uh, being worried about tomorrow?
还是后天的事
Or the day after?
我不担心  雷
I'm not worried, Ray,
什么也不担心
about anything.
那挺好啊
Well, that's good.
后天开始
For a while, day after tomorrow,
我得单独行动一阵子
I'll need to be on my own.
到时候你就能好好学习
That might be a good time for you to learn
如何管好你自己的事
how to mind your own business.
好吧
Well...
在这期间  有什么我能帮上忙的
meantime, there's anything I can do to help,
尽管告诉我
just let me know.
我会的  雷
I'll be sure to let you know, Ray.
我会跟进我那个线人
And I'll follow up on that contact of mine,
希望能拿到你需要的信息
hopefully get the information you need.
我想要
Want,
不是需要
not need.
我什么也不需要  雷
I don't need anything, Ray.
关于我这个人
If there's one thing you should know
你得知道  雷
about me, Ray,
我什么也不需要
it's that I don't need anything.
我想要
I want.
我想要那个信息
And I want that information.
她只愿意给你也是挺可笑的
Kind of funny that she'll only give it to you.
这信息似乎对你很重要
This information seems pretty important to you.
别担心  我会帮你拿到的
Don't worry. I'll get it for you.
而且最好是可靠的信息
And I better be able to trust that information.
她是黑斯廷斯的秘书
She's Hastings' secretary.
他知道的她都知道
She knows what he knows.
玛格丽特
Margaret?
霍克
Hawk.
你今晚走去哪儿
Where are you walking tonight?
我再一次和你的木头同步了
Once again, your log and I are on the same page.
这里今晚应该会有事发生
Supposed to be something happening here tonight.
众星转动
The stars turn...
时间自我呈现
and the time presents itself.
霍克
Hawk,
仔细观察
watch carefully.
我会的  玛格丽特
I will, Margaret.
我太虚弱  没能和你一起去
I'm too weak to go with you.
但顺道来一趟
But stop by.
我给你准备了咖啡和派
I have coffee and pie for you.
得晚一点了  我快到了
Gonna have to be after. I'm almost there now.
请告诉我发生什么事
Please, let me know what happens.
我会的  玛格丽特
I will, Margaret.
晚安  玛格丽特
Good night, Margaret.
那是
未来
还是
那是
过去
有人
来
了
你好
库柏探员
你现在
可以
出去了
你认得我吗
你是劳拉·帕尔默吗
Are you Laura Palmer?
我好像认识她
但有时我的手臂
向后弯
你是谁
Who are you?
我是
劳拉·帕尔默
劳拉·帕尔默已经死了
But Laura Palmer is dead.
我
确实死了
但我以这样的方式活着
我什么时候可以离开
When can I go?
这是
未来
还是说
这是
过去
这是手臂的
进化
我
就是
手臂
而且  我
听起来像
这样
你
还记得
你的
分身吗
他
必须要
在
你
走
之前
回到
你
身上
杰克  过来一下
Jack, come here.
妈的
Shit.
他要进来了  我要挂电话了
He's coming. I have to get off the phone.
宝贝
Hi, baby.
你在跟谁讲电话
Who you talking to?
杰克
Um, Jack.
只是想跟他确认一下
Just making sure I get the job done
我在秘书的车上动的手脚都搞定了
on the secretary's car.
那杰克怎么说
What did Jack say?
他说一切顺利
He said it's all good to go.
我很开心能见到你
I'm happy to see you.
我还以为
I thought maybe you'd
可能你自己跑哪去待了一阵子
gone off on your own for a while,
如你之前所说的
like you were saying.
你见到我很高兴吗  达雅
You're happy to see me, Darya?
高兴  宝贝
Yeah, baby.
真好  达雅
That's nice, Darya.
雷本来打算今天下午跟我见面的
Ray was supposed to meet me this afternoon.
-但他没出现  -是吗
- He never showed. - Oh, yeah?
是的
Yeah.
你那枪放哪了  达雅
Where's that .45 of yours, Darya?
我把它放我床头了
I've got it here by the bed.
怎么了吗
What's up?
我可能要借用一下
Might want to borrow it for a job.
我的就是你的
What's mine is yours.
达雅  杰克死了
Darya, Jack is dead.
两小时之前在他把车弄好后  我把他杀了
I killed Jack two hours ago after he wired the car.
别动
Don't move...
一丁点都不要动
...one muscle.
我要放个东西给你听  达雅
I'm gonna play something for you, Darya.
我们都会觉得有趣的东西
I think we'll both find this interesting.
达雅  是你吗
Darya, is that you?
雷  你他妈在哪啊
Ray, where the hell are you?
我在联邦监狱  南达科塔州
Federal prison, South Dakota.
搞什么鬼  你犯了什么事  雷
What the fuck? What did you do, Ray?
过州边境的时候携带了武器
Carried weapons over the state line.
我搞砸了  挑在最差的时机
I fucked up, the worst possible moment.
你怎么给我打电话的
How are you calling me?
这是个一次性手机  不用担心
This is a burner. Don't worry about it.
没有人偷听
Nobody's listening.
库柏那边  我们要做些什么
So what do we do about Cooper?
杰弗里斯打过给我
I got another call from Jeffries.
如果库柏明晚还活着  你一定要杀了他
You have to hit Cooper if he's still around tomorrow night.
现在  达雅  你必须这么做
That means you now, Darya. You have to do this.
操
Fuck.
操  他刚停车  操
Fuck, I think his car just pulled up.Fuck!
看看明天什么情况吧
Let's see what happens tomorrow.
如果形势所迫  我会搞定他的
If I have to, I'll take him out.
妈的  他要进来了  我要挂电话了
Shit, he's coming. I got to get off the phone.
你是要杀了我吗
Are you going to kill me?
是的  达雅
Yes, Darya.
操
Shit!
达雅...
Darya...
是谁雇你和雷来杀我的
who hired you and Ray to kill me?
我不知道
I don't know.
我发誓  我不...
I swear, I don't...
雷知道
Ray knows.
我不知道  他没告诉过我
I don't know. He never told me.
你真指望我会相信
Do you really expect me to believe that
雷进监狱是因为持枪跨越州界吗
Ray's in prison for carrying guns over a state line?
达雅  看着我
Darya, look at me.
这事想来还挺有趣的
This is quite an interesting thing to think about.
游戏开始了
The game begins.
他说过他们为什么想杀死我吗
Did he say why they want me dead?
没有  我不知道为什么
No, I don't know why.
他们有多想我死  他们给了你们多少钱
How much do they want me dead? What are they paying you?
我们分了50万
We'd split a half a million.
我不想这么干的
I wouldn't have done it.
我告诉过雷
I just said that to Ray.
闭嘴  达雅
Shut up, Darya.
但是...
But...
你说过你明天要去某个地方
you said you were going away somewhere tomorrow.
明天
Tomorrow,
我本来会被拉回一个叫黑色小屋的地方
I'm supposed to get pulled back into what they call the Black Lodge.
但我不会回那里了
But I'm not going back there.
我想了个计划
I've got a plan for that one.
但雷那个混蛋进监狱这件事...
But this prison thing with that fucker Ray...
达雅   雷是从黑斯廷斯的秘书那里得到的消息吗
Darya, did Ray get that information from Hastings' secretary?
他有和你提过具体坐标吗
Did he ever mention coordinates to you?
我不知道那是什么
I don't know what that is.
地理坐标  数字  字母
Geographical coordinates, numbers, letters.
这些东西可以救你一命
They could save your life.
他说过她告诉了他一些事情  但我不知道是什么
He said she told him something, but I don't know what.
有人给你看过这个吗
Anybody ever show this to you before?
你知道这是什么吗
Do you know what this is?
你之前有见过类似的东西吗
Did you ever see anything like this?
我想要的就是这个
This is what I want.
你现在是要杀了我吗
Are you gonna kill me now?
是的  达雅
Yes, Darya.
菲利普
Phillip?
你迟到了
You're late.
我也无能为力
Couldn't be helped.
在纽约我错过了你
I missed you in New York,
但我看你还在鹿角镇
but I see you're still in Buckhorn.
而你还是不知所踪  是不是
And you're still nowhere, is that correct?
你见到了少校加兰德·布里格斯
You met with Major Garland Briggs.
你怎么知道的
How did you know that?
菲利普
Phillip?
实际上  我打电话给你是为了道别的
Actually, I just called to say good-bye.
你是菲利普·杰弗里斯吧
This is Phillip Jeffries, right?
你明天就得回来了
You're going back in tomorrow,
然后我会再次和鲍勃在一起
and I will be with Bob again.
你是谁
Who is this?
探员编号
密码
鹿角镇
南达科他州
扬克顿联邦监狱
搜索结果
扬克顿联邦监狱  南达科他州
扬克顿联邦监狱
机构
姓名
号码
扬克顿联邦监狱
下载
下载完成
谁
Yeah?
是我
It's me.
我需要你来把六号房清理一下
I need you to clean up in room six.
一切都清理了
Everything.
达雅
Darya?
真是个好消息
That's good news.
我太嫉妒那个婊子了
I was getting so jealous of that bitch.
那就去把你的丈夫找来
Then go get your husband.
几天后我需要你和哈齐去某个地方
I need you and Hutch in a certain area in a few days.
我会通知你的
I'll get word to you.
好的  老板
Okay, boss.
香塔尔
Chantal,
过来
come here.
你又好又湿
You're nice and wet.
一
遍
又
一遍
鲍勃
快走
找到
劳拉
有点
不对劲
我的
分身
不
存
在
好奇怪
Weird.
他去哪儿了
Where is he?
这说明我可以
Does this, by any chance, mean that
跟你一起进去吗
I can go in there with you?
我又带了两杯拿铁来
I brought us two lattes again.
枪炮酒吧
这地方不错吧
Great place, isn't it?
是啊  这地方真赞
Yeah, it's the dog's bollocks in here.
-你要什么啤酒  -都可以
- What kind of beer do you want? - Oh, I'll have whatever.
两瓶冰殖民地
Two ice-cold Colonials.
不  伙计们
No, you guys,
我的女儿不该和他交往
my daughter is with the wrong guy.
你开什么玩笑  大家都爱史蒂文
Are you kidding me? Everybody loves Steven.
你不了解贝基  从她脸上就看得出来
You don't know Becky. I can see it on her face.
非常不对劲
There is something really wrong.
这是她的人生
It's her life.
这边
Hey, over there.
那是詹姆斯  他又盯着你看了
There's James. He's staring at you again.
詹姆斯喜欢你吗
Does James have a thing for you?
那家伙有点不对劲
There's something wrong with that guy.
他没有不对劲
There's nothing wrong with him.
詹姆斯遭遇了摩托车车祸
James was in a motorcycle accident.
现在他很安静
He's just quiet now.
詹姆斯还是很酷
James is still cool.
他一直很酷
He's always been cool.